question_data = [
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": "Does Python allow function overloading.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": "Are arrays in Python resizable.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": "Is CSS a programming language.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": "Does the break statement in Python only exit the innermost loop.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": "Does HTML provide a way to create interactive web pages.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": " In Python, is it possible to use a list comprehension to generate a list of prime numbers.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": " In Java, can a method be both abstract and final.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": "Can a Python function have a variable number of arguments.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": "Can a function return multiple values in Python.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "science: computers",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficuity": "medium",
        "question": "Are dictionaries ordered collections in Python.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answer": [
            "True"
        ]
    },


]
